Hello. Good morning. I just woke up. Hey, good sleep.
Yeah, I came in my, woke up, my tablet was on the floor. It fell off and didn't start up for a
Good morning, everybody.
Good morning.
Just have Mr. Mojito's first bath.
Oh, who's Mr. Mojito is the cat or dog?
Mr. Mojito, how cute.
Hey.
Mr. Mojito.
Hi, Jamie.
Hi, Taro is just Taro does.
Always a five-week-old kid and how cute.
Hey, Mr. Tricks is here.
Hi, bad boy breeze.
Jamie, hey, Michael, how are you?
Michael, I haven't seen you.
Hi.
Hi, everybody.
Good to see everybody.
Nice, beautiful breeze going through here today.
Bad boy breeze, is that your setting up breeze?
Yeah, Trix is sitting here next to me.
I had a good sleep though.
It's a nice day.
The whack pack vanilla dice, baby.
Hi.
How are we doing today, guys?
Feel good.
I had a nice cleansing bath last night, a spiritual bath.
I got some sage.
You know all the all the bad energies clear the
Energy the space. Hello, Jim. How are you? Good to see ya? God bless America. I
Have some speedos that look like your
Hi guys, good to see everybody
Hello, okay. I have cigarettes today poison frog. What's up? Hey, what's up? Hey Maya?
Hi everybody.
How are we doing today? Hey J-Dog. Welcome everybody. Let's see I got the link up but I don't have the
hi mermaid let's see mermaid where's mermaid oh there's a player that's up guys
let's see thank you he-man what's up yeah thank you so much he-man
my yesterday we had a really great day hey Amanda we had a great day yesterday because
We had new members in the last couple of days, I think we had about 20 members almost.
That's really cool.
Thank you for everyone that gifted memberships.
I gifted some too.
So we should see some more green names of the chat. Hey Michael wants to come on up.
Say hi to me on the panel.
There you got it.
How are we doing?
Tiff's husband's name, we have to let me know.
Oh, if you get docs or something,
just let me know, I'll delete the comments.
And the panel's not supposed to be doxing either,
so I apologize if there was doxing.
You know, just let me know.
But it was last night, hold on.
Just let me know. I'm sorry. I did like I was not here at the very end of the show
I didn't fall asleep. It was Paige. I think Chris K
Who else was on panel guys last night? Is page a Chris K?
There's somebody else. Mr. Big Pipe tried to get back on but I kept bringing him on he wouldn't he didn't do it
He wouldn't talk so I
Don't know what that was about. I kept bringing him on
Tried I don't know if he was
My neck okay, look okay, I know I'm sitting down a little bit, I know my 1% on my, my phone right now, so hopefully it needs to be going the other direction.
I'm okay, my neck's fine, happy hump day.
Who is T.Y., oh yeah, T.Y.
I found his channel. He's like a sports betting and the trap house channel. He apparently has been being hacked and having his channels deleted. It's pretty scary, guys.
That can happen. The way you fell asleep, you're worried about be hurting. Oh, I fell asleep in a weird position last night. Oh, classy sassy. It's because I am modern everybody except just like, you know, I think I have three mods.
Hey Michael
Did anyone hear my element doesn't hear him hold on hold on can't hear anybody
gentlemen
Yes, sir
Good morning. Good morning. Good morning. How are you guys? I hear you now good
Good morning. Everyone are you guys doing good? Do you hear me? Yes? Okay? Now here? Yeah, I got
Just getting up now. I'm just getting up now getting the day started
Get my coffee. How you guys doing?
Pretty good good good look up to a bunch of positive
Yeah, a lot of positive city. Hi guys. Yeah, sorry about my I couldn't hear before. Yeah, so
How'd you sleep? I slept really good
Nice, I had a big I had a macaroni and cheese
grilled cheese sandwich
So good macaroni and cheese sandwich. I've never heard of that
Yeah, macaroni and cheese was grilled, it was from like a little place, all they make is grilled cheese sandwiches, so I had last night.
What are your thoughts on grilled cheese with tomato soup?
Oh, it's great, it's great.
It's good, right?
Classic, what's it called, one of those comfort foods, the comfort food.
Yep.
Big double
What's it called again, that's for Pulp Fiction. It's called living Mac
The big double cheese
It's called it's actually called it's called the double cheeseburger from McDonald's, right? I don't know Michael
Real cheese is very good. Yeah. Yeah, that's a good Michael
A little bit. Yeah, I think I've been gone for a while
Do you have?
Be the brush who up to the day actually and I was like
It's me was like every day. Oh, yeah, she was like everybody knows Michael linguine and I'm a yo stop doxing him
I'm like what I can't say Michael linguine. I'm a yo dude. What the fuck and she's like what that's just
She's not a real name. She just likes to say the word we
Know you're I thought that was like a real name. I didn't know it was a fake name
No, no
False delete
Any girl Jen Jen
Are you good? Don't make me sound a little a little different.
Who me? Yeah. No, I'm good.
Are you still mad at me? You were kind of mad at me last time.
Who you talking about me? Yeah. No, I'm not. Thank you. I'll never be mad at you.
Did you see I was a bit you said I was a bitch
It's okay
Okay, okay, I
Think Michael man, this is all a bit
Yeah, do I know that?
That nobody looks a lot like Lenny Kravitz I've seen nobody before he does
I don't know, I never noticed that.
Yo, so, Psyche, I'm joining today because I've heard a couple people are like, I don't
want to say they're taking like a strike against you, maybe more like a break.
Oh, yeah, I've heard about that.
Who is?
I don't know if I want to put the names out there, but a couple people are taking like
I'm joining the panel from listening
So I will I probably notice about you just some just uh, what it's a seag and mr. Bigpipes
No, uh, Sam and elbow a couple of people from the this way
Yeah, they're all they're all gonna take a hiatus they said, okay, well, that's fine
That's fine
That's not the elder yesterday. I'm talking to Sammy. I don't know. It's like people like, you know
People could focus on their own shows first. I know that's French
Well, no, they said they like just listening. They're gonna like tune away from this
Okay, well, it's good
Take all the take out they'll come back if they come back it will come back fresh and you go
They don't come back. They were not my they're not my
friends to begin with right
Let's see. Do I know they're fans?
I'll join back and
Not even uh
Recognize what they said
And Elda just donated five memberships yesterday
And he's a and he's a third mod so
He did acknowledge that he was the mod
No, no, he did say that yesterday so it all went down on
Sam answering
They're talking about you for a little bit nothing bad
I just you came across the topic and they're like, yeah, you know, let's take a little break from sight
You know, it's just it doesn't seem like that's where I should be right now. Maybe it'll change later
Okay, well my feelings are so incredibly hurt
You said this one time he said as long as I have one fucking viewer. I'm still gonna be here
Yeah, yeah
What if I have one troll I just have one one I just have one troll in the chat this is truly me the entire shit
I'd be funny because I just want one person in the chat this truly me I'd be funny
No, but I love you guys like most people like I kept this one of the days I came in
that is like there's just so many people came in and said hi hey Mary Hopkins good to see you
so many people said hi I was just like wow look at all my friends look at look at everyone come
in and say hi to me this morning so um so yeah
Yeah, yeah, I'm totally I want people to go where they want to go. I'm not I think so seriously
I'm not trying to coerce or force anybody here or you know, anybody can go where they want to go
Never watch me
I'm not gonna worry about it. It's like, you know, yeah, I mean, who knows why they're saying that it's like, I don't know
it's like, you know
salmon has a as a
More you know, like a hundred people in his chat every time so
You know, I'm just a little fish
He sounds strange Michael's fine. It's just he I think his microphone thing a little different
He will think you're using a voice changer or something. No, that's what I'm saying Michael. You do sound a little off. I don't know
Okay
No, I'm good. No
Good good, I don't know in you guys
All right
Michael McLeven doesn't form up. No. Yeah, he doesn't I
Just see him without a shirt off before are people still form bombing. That's still a thing
Yeah, I got form on yesterday. I got a hard bomb yesterday. What?
Yeah, I think so did I get my guys remember I got I think I did a form bomb yesterday for
Or maybe the day before yesterday, I don't know, like on Kate's show, she was sending AMC over here to N-word bomb, porn bomb, and she was like laughing and congratulating him and stuff.
Yeah, so it's pretty much only that one person, you know, I recognize his voice.
And I'm pretty sure Kate modded though, that's crazy.
No, okay, it's not modded. I don't know. I only have Jamie's Cowboys traveling gypsy and
Yeah
Amc's basically Kate's attack the attack dog. Yeah, I
Don't know it's like I would I would never mess with anybody else like say oh don't donate to this person
Don't donate to this person this person doesn't deserve this person
I would never say that about anybody anybody, you know
But Kate saying that about me and other people other people are saying oh don't donate don't donate it's like
I don't know. I've never even heard of anybody, any people,
contact readers saying that about people. It's just, it's
ridiculous.
She's on her deathbed. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh yeah. I mean,
that's real nice. Like someone, someone's deathly ill. Here,
let's let's let's troll and harass. I mean, is that, is she
okay? Is she really ill?
Yes, he's real. I know I haven't seen Jim making a lot of time. She's she's very ill. She just screamed yesterday
Oh, she did. I know that she's another she's ill. I'm not sure exactly. I don't I don't want to I don't think to the level that they're saying
I'm like, oh my gosh, he's on her bed. You know, I don't know
Yeah, well, I mean, it's like that's fine to say
Yeah, so I'm not sure. No, this is not nice, you know
Like living that live, you know, worry about your own show. It's like, you know, I I never I always let you use my content
I mean, you know, by like charge you or or you know, threaten you or anything. No, I'm like, I'm like, I just
gracious enough to
Let you make fun of me and and put me down and stuff. I don't care. You can use my content
You can restream me whatever
But have I missed anything?
You miss anything. Um, what do you think? What do you think?
Yes, sir.
Yeah, you kind of miss you miss a little bit. I mean you got you got you got poor mom. Yes
Well, no Michael. I don't know if you miss this uh psyche. I don't know if you know
Uh, do you guys know raging demon, correct?
Oh, yeah raging demon. Yeah. Oh, yeah
Do you know about the whole raging demon and diamond?
Oh, yeah
Pk, uh, pkg
Beata
She did it. What was it yesterday or day before yesterday or something?
Um, I know I
I heard is that you I don't know she called she calls them up beat up beat up call them out
Yeah, maybe like two days ago or yesterday
Yeah, that's last week there was like last week there was like a 40-diamond shared like you know
She was on the phone with him at the time and it for like the last six hours
they had hundreds of messages and
Why then I heard they're radiating but then I heard yes
But that I heard someone each if the other ones ass. I'm not sure. I mean, no, no, they haven't met up
Okay, they have shared nudes
Okay
That's crazy
Diamonds, are you here if you want to oh here we go
Here we go
No, no, so this is their new names psyche diamond is now called
raging diamond raging diamonds and
Lurdy demon it's learning demon. Yes
Like that
Yeah, I like I came up with that you know I can
Okay. Love you, Barry. Thank you. I miss you too. Come back. Oh my God. Nothing. What? What's wrong?
Just very very flip flops. Like always shing on the channel. He's like you got dirty toes dirty fingernails and then he's like
Oh, I love you. I love you. So yeah, you're good. Is Barry here. You said Barry right now. I know that is
But I don't know why I said it. Oh, I don't know why you said it
I was I think I was not in the room. I said I was reading Doug says Michael
I was saying had him I said I had a Mary not Barry. Come on. Oh, you said Barry though. Come on
My he was actually pictures of amc with his head shaved and another man's name and on his forehead because he was getting bullied online. Oh
What?
Terrible
Well, what was that story?
Story I heard yesterday. Hold on
Yeah
Yeah, someone called in and said that they said JT
like was bullying this like mentally kind of a little bit like handicapped
Person the person that's not all there. I don't know if he was just you know had mental problems or you know
But he, like, he and LD, like, catfished him to, like, fly down to Florida to meet somebody he thought was a woman of his dreams.
And it was all, like, a thing that humiliated him, like, you know, like, there was nobody there.
They had this guy fly all the way down there to meet this woman.
Kind of sounds kind of cool, I don't know.
Oh, happy game month or whatever it's called. What is it?
Well, it's Pride Month, but it's all, you know, a few more days left.
That's like a very good thing to you
and
Yeah
I thought you were gonna say it back or something. Oh happy Friday month. I mean, I I mean, yeah
I mean, I really don't know. I mean, what do I do this month? I were I were like a
a rainbow flag
Yeah, we're more the American flag speedo. That was my
Fourth of July guys. Yeah, and salmon has been denying the fact that he was here when you went to
I don't know if you can see him here.
He's denying you to the chair.
Yeah, that was just somebody that used my avatar
and they went up there as me.
That was me.
Oh, sure.
Sam, man.
Oh, my god.
Wow.
Don't be embarrassed.
Everyone liked what they saw.
They're like, no, that wasn't me.
That was just somebody used the avatar.
That wasn't me.
Like, dude.
He hasn't saved all this.
I'm his desktop
The photo on his desktop. I mean the shower
Very diamond to attack Kristine summer use Miguel's messages 30 down in negative vibes and energy. Oh, she did hate to traveling gypsy. How are you?
Sam was there at the same time was imagining he was in the shower with the ass. I could bet that he was
Robbing
It was quite a day it was does quite a day
Yeah, thank you for having me, Dixie.
Howard you have you been you met up that person your friend again. They've been coming up to change or clean the pipes
You know, no, she she's been helping clean the house like she she cleaned my kitchen and she brought a vacuum over last night
You said the man the other day, you know, well, no, it's it's it's him and his it is like his baby mama
And then she lives nearby. He was kind of further away. What I thought I thought it was by himself
And I thought he was gay. Do you got clean lady?
No, she's not a cleaning lady. She's just she's just a friend that that is helping me like you know
she's like really into
Okay, and and she's helped like you clean my kitchen and you know, why?
in the living room
No, she's she's very she's very kind. She's like helping me. You know like for what?
I'm sorry, but if I that were me, I'm expecting something
Yeah
Well we
It's cool. I think she she really she really likes she really likes cleaning so she's helping me out a lot
Yeah, like if I had caffeine today or something. No
The DMT couple yes, they have a DMT pen and I hit it one time yesterday yesterday
I wasn't in the best mood for it, but the night a couple days before Wow, it was just like so crazy
It was just out of the trim balls
a person may know. Yeah. Yeah. She's under the goodness of her heart. Yeah.
She, uh, people, people do look at people, do look at, I'm just very lucky.
People look out for me and they want to help me. Um, and once, um, you know,
I think it will really help a lot. I'll be able to maintain things either.
Yeah. If you can take it out, take it.
Yeah. So, thank you. Yeah.
Uh, real quick, did you like my promo during the day when I was like,
What about that? Is that TOS?
Huh?
What? I'm rubbing my dick right now, is that TOS?
Did you like that promo?
No, I mean it was like, I don't know. You're just kind of mocking me like you know, I
If I worry about TOS, it's like that's for me to where it's not it's not your channel
No, you have to worry about TOS violation. It's only my channel. It's only my channel, right?
There's a promo though. It was a promo like a shoe. You've seen WWE, right? Yeah
What were you promoting? It was just a promo of the channel in a
Me being a heel, you know
Yeah, people don't want to hear the whole lovey-dovey-dovey, you know, sometimes you need that little spark
Everybody knows this channel nothing but good here, you know
Hey Christine
Oh
Hi, Vanna that lady joins. I'm out of here. I'm just got to say that right now. It's Christine joins
Literally right now. I'm up and out of here that I can't stand that lady as Christine ever joined though
Oh, yeah
She'll be like, um, can you get your dog out of my lawn?
I'm totally like doing it right now and you're your creatures on my lawn right now. I don't appreciate that
Hey, how are you?
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
I don't know how to adult. I just
don't know what to say. Oh,
Arthur. Oh, silly, silly, silly.
Everybody laughed about everybody
like that. See? Yes. See, sometimes
sometimes you don't have to
you don't have to listen to what
just be the adult. Pretty much she was telling you don't come on here. Pretty much, wasn't he?
Yeah. Michael, have you met Cristian? Have you talked to Cristian? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Did he even know you came up to me? Had you come up to me? And his beautiful, significant other.
Yeah. Thank you. I appreciate that. Yeah, she's lovely.
Yeah, Michael's okay sometimes. No, I'm just I agree. I don't know what I was gonna say, but he's a pretty good guy
I know I've done Michael probably for over a year in about a year because I met him on here on
Benny's when I was on Benny's last year
Honestly, I would say like a year and a half almost two years
Well
Yeah, I think I might have maybe maybe it was almost you know, it was like a little bit earlier last year, but yeah
I mean, I found Benny shortly after the the new year last year
But I talked to Michael on a panel once and I think I hit on him the first night
Then he reacted in a friendly way and I was like wow
I was like no one's ever reacting in a friendly way. I thought I always thought it was cool for that
Yeah, we have a nice nice 33 people in chat right now awesome guys
Arthur was leading anyway, he baited Christie to join 3D test. Arthur's brilliant.
Yeah, but like I said, I always join in the beginning before it gets too hectic.
Yeah.
Yeah, but it seems like it's going pretty well this morning or yeah, I just I woke up my it's 415. It's even oh my gosh
Oh my gosh, I thought it was over. I thought it was 10 a.m. Now. It's 1 15 a.m. Okay. Wow
I'm only gonna say for a few minutes my I have a son who's
Spent my entire morning in the ER with them. Oh my gosh
Okay, yes dad went up there now so
He's an adult, but you know, he he's having a lot of issues. So we just didn't think it was good
You're breaking up Michael, honey
It will be they're trying to fix them up. We'll say they're trying they may keep them
They're talking they wanted to keep them, but he's very adamant. He's not staying. I know Maya. It's all good
Everybody got a laugh on it. That's all that matters. Here's Carl on the back. I do too. Is it that's not mine
Is that yours? It's here. It's here. Are you think okay? Yeah
Got a lot of parking lots around here. So
Yeah, mermaid. He's still in there trying to get everything under control. I
Don't like being in places where people are sick because then I get sick
Yeah, then you don't feel well yourself. I
Don't have an immune system
My immune system comes in a bottle every week that I infuse
So germs germs and I don't do well together
Yeah, so you have to be extra careful with with around
Yeah, and things like that. Yeah, I do
Do I do but you know, I've been good. I've been hospitalized since like
2019 so that's a good thing I
Think 2019 we finally figured out the right cocktails
Great combination for you. Yeah, it was next impossible to get him to go today
And I'm like, yeah, you know, and I don't send people to the ER
You did not go to the ER unless it is life or you know limb threatening
So I don't believe in the ER, but yeah, he had to go today
So dad's up there now there. They've got a specialist in there
So hopefully they'll figure it out and he can come home because he's not going to be a good patient in the ER
I promise that
But what's up anything else? Oh shoot. I'll be right back. So I gotta take this call. Okay, Christian
Yeah, when you're in hospital it sucks the doctors tell you you need to stay another day every day. Yeah
Yeah, I haven't been to the hospital quite a long time
Probably
I don't think I have some other bait.
So what's that key, if you know?
If you know.
What's going on with the raging demon, Beto?
Well, you know, it's like, he just comes in,
and he always says terrible things.
He's like, hey, hey, Ilya.
Yeah, he just says terrible things to her and to Beto.
Or when she's in the room, he'll start screaming like,
That calls her bad names and she, uh, you know,
you know, why, why is she calling you a fag, you know?
No, I don't, I don't know, because he's, because with 30 diamond, you know,
like they're, she's saying he's with 30 diamonds or something.
Oh, I have no idea what that I'm not, I'm not a hundred percent sure.
Like, wow, you think he's on at age.
Hey, Ilya.
Yeah, let's see. Oh, I don't know. I'm making a coffee or something or a bagel or something at the bagel shop
But see do I have any weed left? I do have a little bit weed left
Clean off my table. I
Had yeah, finish up most my weed. Why is your hat bigger than your entire head? Oh come on
Do the thing is I haven't said anything bad about anybody and yet the trolls they always want to talk shit about me
Yeah, I come in peace. I don't get it. I
Don't get it. I
Don't get it
No, but it's no, but it's all gone. They
Oh good usually my old self
I would be like, you know, running back and stuff like that, but it's doggy, I'm not worried about it.
Let's see.
Oh, come on, chat be nice to Michael.
Having me back? When was the last time I was on here?
Maybe a couple weeks ago, maybe two to three weeks. Oh, it's a couple weeks probably a couple weeks. I would say a month ago
You see you haven't been on a month. I don't know
It's maybe a couple weeks you shouldn't joke about how it sounds his older girlfriend might have him beat up. Oh
You got lovely followers
You got lovely followers. Yeah, well, I've a wonderful chat. Let's see if you like a reading Michael. I got your reading
Yeah here with Michael. Yeah, okay
Villain sick
Okay, let's see
Michael the star they're getting clarity about something you're receiving the truth about something
This is also make a wish wish on a star
There's some star watching out for you
This is the star
It's number 17 is a star, a star says,
just as a queen's magic mirror also responds honestly
to any question asked, star represents clarity,
hope, and the power of truth.
The star indicates you're coming out of a period
of a confusion and an uncertainty.
While this chapter in your life may have been difficult
to star as a guiding light here to illuminate
the way forward.
Though you may not have the magic mirror at your disposal,
the tarot card encourages you to pursue
and embrace the truth.
Hey, Flirty.
You've been watching Titanic 666 with Raging Demon this whole time and people talk about
you.
Come on, floating diamond.
Everyone wants to know what's going on.
Everyone's curious.
Okay.
Make a wish.
What else we got from Michael?
Michael, come through for Michael.
Okay.
Come through for Michael, please.
Oh.
Queen of coins
This is a queen of coins
There's one with a crocodile. There's a queen of coins. Okay, queen of pentacles. So, you know, I think this is like, you know
You're probably with a woman that can help you
She's abundant and she can help you be abundant. She can inspire you. She can have great ideas
And and things will work out around her. The Queen of Coins is smart and calculating figure who cultivates material abundance for herself as the owner of a pawn shop Madame Medusa
exemplifies the entrepreneurial spirit of the Queen of Coins. The card represents prosperity, success in business and a happy home life.
That's good news. You know, I think that might be experienced a happy home life and some abundance right now.
One more card
Oh there goes, okay. Oh four of cups, okay, so this is like you know
This is about
You're gonna get the right offer, but there might be some offers made before that that you'll reject
Okay, so you don't have to accept the first offer or the second offer the third offer it might be the fourth, you know, so don't
but there is some kind of
Some kind of a choice you have to make and
You know, I think you might be bored also and there's going to be some kind of offer made that's going to wake you up a little bit and make you happy.
Let me see, that's the four of cups.
Four of cups says, there is a decision to be made, the four of cups tarot cards reminder to consider your options carefully.
Remember, you don't have to accept everything you're offered. Listen to your intuition.
Don't be afraid to decline opportunities that don't feel right for you.
Okay, so I hope that made some sense.
Give you some guidance this morning
Good
Yeah
So just look out for that
The opera you've been waiting for so hey three is a raging demon here, too. Let me see
Hey, what's up raging demon has everyone doing?
guys when I
Come up and chat you're welcome
Yeah, you're watching Titanic car a car the chat. Let's see it for the chat
Okay for the chat we have the six of swords, okay
Six of swords and who so who's that that's that Cinderella's mother? It looks like some kind of some kind of guard up, okay?
To chat you might relate to this card
Says swords in the case you recently been through a difficult time unexpected setbacks can be demoralizing. Don't let them
Do you really completely the situation is?
Salvageable, so do not despair
So if anyone's feelings things are hopeless or they're helpless or something
You know all hope is not lost always always remember
Maybe you can still still make things right
Oh, it's a horror movie, not Titan.
Oh, it's 666 Titan.
Okay, okay, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I just saw Titan.
I didn't know.
I know it was 666 Titan.
A couple more.
Let's give it a couple more for the chat.
You stretched that.
Michael stretched out 30 diamonds e-hole.
What does that mean?
Okay, what do we got?
Oh, oh, we got this fool card.
I never got the fool.
Who is this?
Is this Hercules?
Is that Hercules?
There's the fool.
Look, I think he's got like these two little angel
Angel in the Devil, he's got these, you know, he listens to both, is that foolish or is
that wise, you know, it's a, it says, Yuma's solidly built henchman, Crunk, is enthusiastic
and eager to do his best.
However, he often blunders his missions by goofing off or getting distracted.
Are the spinach puffs burning?
The Fool represents someone who, like Cronk,
is excited to embark on a new adventure,
but whose inexperience and naivete
sometimes trips them up along the way.
Says you're on the precipice of an exciting journey,
with a spring in your step and your head held high,
you're ready to pursue a new goal with limitless potential.
The Fool tarot card advises you to balance
your bubbly optimism with a little common sense.
If you stay level-headed, focused,
and double-checked the labels
Yuma's potion bottles, there's no telling where the new path will take you.
Hey, Shemali. You know, so it's like maybe
after the typical time, there's a new journey. It's like you just step into it.
Okay, and keep going forward because then we got Correlativeville,
the chariot, full speed ahead, right?
It says, the chariot represents determination, unrelenting focus, and willpower, much like
the formidable, fashion-loving, cruelty-vill, who doesn't let anything stop her from getting
what she wants, not even a car chase in the snow.
Obstacles won't faze you now, you're in hot pursuit of your goals, nothing will stand
in your way for long.
Don't let yourself get distracted, what you want may seem just out of reach now, but putting
your pedal to the metal will give you the last little boost you need to succeed.
There you go
You're free you're free you guys hope you guys enjoy those
IVs of acid rate medicated. Yeah
Wengie's genius code
Yeah, we were charmed to nobody
No
Everyone's shy. I was too shy today. Whoof
Booping is good to you out here. Let me see
Who boop boop booping? So what's the chat? How's the chat doing?
Um, we got like 20 new members six yesterday
three new members
you know, we had some
We've had people do some um, some gifting of memberships. Thank you so much for those
And, yeah, most of the gifted members do come in here,
and so they're active people, so that's pretty cool.
Have we started the boof shit?
Is that a patrol?
What is the boof shit?
What's everyone talking about?
No, oh, Doug, Michael will not.
I don't agree with that.
So how is your week been?
Who's your sister-in-law, let me see.
Sorry, the chats.
Oh, using jokes through the anal route.
Yeah, you can use a, is it suppository?
Or they call it booty bumps?
Oh, boofing and pitting substances in your anus.
Yeah, I think they call them booty bumps out here.
You just take like a syringe without the needle on it
Squirt it up there. I don't think I've tried it though
You didn't do fiberglass. Oh my gosh beer has anyone anyone had a
But what Howard sir used to have Howard seems to have a vagina bomb or something like that
What was what was didn't Howard Stern used to like?
Have some kind of like
You can dig make a vagina ball. I don't know. You ever heard of that?
That's what I know
But I know but chugged no, I don't think so. I don't think so
Goofy is for the wicked. Yeah
cooter shooter
You're a woman talking to tampons in vodka. Oh, Michael. Let's see how you even respond. Yeah
Well, no one's talking about you
Some people talking talking about people
You can't believe it
Michael is currently on Venus. Yeah, you're on live naked Nick you are you are Nick?
What are you wearing?
Are you on chatter bait?
I heard somebody say that somebody said oh, I saw you on chatter bait
Anyway, I'll be back
Really where the gas station will put my guy
Like four beers. I'll you I see Michael and
I guess
Are you
Okay, guys, let's see 38 people in chat
I don't know about Mike. I'm next camera, but I can't hear his
Can't hear his what's it called? It's microphones
They hear me talking
How's everyone's day? Hope he's not driving. Yeah, I don't know. Maybe I'll get a coffee at a place like he's close over
Closing 130 so much. I'd love probably
We see their hours
Okay, Noah's bagels close or close the 2 p.m. Okay, hold on. That's Manhattan
You don't have it and here we go
Oh, I've been noticed it's Einstein bagel
And send bagels see closed
Well, it closes too early.
Is the M.O.S. not even supposed to blunt through his anus?
How's everyone doing? Well, what do I do? What do I do?
Have enough
Figurates I think
What do you guys what are you?
it's going it's going well you haven't vexed i'll read i'll read them for you if you like
It'd be your first reading, okay
When from the chat
I really have to do it though I keep saying good morning
Okay, we got Bex, you got the Sun card, okay, Sun
So it's very happy card. You know the Sun is a very positive card
Probably one of the most positive cards in the deck. It's always Harold's Good Things and says
Tarnota, the fearsome giant crab from the realm of monsters, glows like the sun when
he covers his enormous shell with priceless riches of bright jewels.
The sun represents unbridled joy, triumph, and happiness, where all feelings displayed
by Tamato's when he celebrates his hoard of shiny treasures.
So it says, Jules, gems, and gold cause Tamatoa to light up with pure delight.
What makes you feel this way?
When are you happiest? The sun encourages you to prioritize your own joy. If the sun is drawn
during a terror reading, seeking clarity about a big project or goal, the card is a very positive
sign. Your optimism and an ineptimal glow, an immeasurable glow will inspire others and
make you success. So shine on. Okay, we got the seven of swords. Okay, seven of swords.
Seven of swords can indicate some kind of some kind of theft or you need to like very carefully examine any kind of contract
It says seven of swords represents sneaky behavior
Are you trying to get away with something if not an unsavory character might be trying to pull the wool over your eyes?
Trust your instincts and stay vigilant
Okay
Seven of swords and
We've got this Queen of Swords, and we again have Cinderella's mother, you know, the Queen
of Swords is like, you know, you may find out about something like that, this is the
Queen of Swords, notice how to cut people out of her energy, out of her life, she's
an intelligent, independent, self-assured, like ladies remain, she's a clever, composed
person who shouldn't be underestimated, the tarot card reminds you to trust yourself,
you're more capable than you give yourself credit for.
And you are
All of us are
Hope you enjoyed that
What's wrong Michael? Oh
Doug are you picking on Michael?
No, you can't just pull it out or you might if it was chatter bait. Yes, but you can like I don't think you should your butthole or your wiener
Make sure you all get fresh air and yeah, I got the I got the fresh air flowing through my house
Yeah, you're welcome Bex
How's everyone doing? Beautiful cats are around me today.
Hey Lola.
Lola.
Hi.
How's everyone doing?
Lenore Tricks, oh, Lenore's outside, I think.
Tricks is right here, Tricks is right here.
Oh, Lenore's over there, Lenore's over there.
Lenore likes a little place next to my computer.
Lenore likes to be outside right now,
but there are gardeners out and everything.
Okay
So how are you guys?
Hey Arthur
How's everyone doing?
a few cards.
Okay, you got the true love card.
I don't know if you, if you have your true love there's some kind of maybe interference or somebody that's jealous or something.
So usually the lover's card, this true love card,
says true love
Card represents faded
Connections love and harmonious partnerships in a relationship theme reading it signifies a great connection a perfect match often the true love card indicates an important decision or crossroads
Consider your options carefully. You'll get your happily ever after
Okay
We have the hermit and so this may have to do with
We're spending some time getting some more alone time quality time
Recharging with drawing from the from the manness of the world
Says alone time is called for when the hermit card shows up if you've been swept up in the hustle bustle of life
The hermit's a clear sign to slow things down for a little while make time to reflect
on where you are in life and think about where you want to go.
Journal, plan a mini vacation, or take a day off for self-care.
They'll come out of this little break
feeling refreshed, recharged, and ready to take on the world.
Finally, we got,
we had the six of coins, but it came reverse.
Okay, so six of coins reversed.
Someone's not being generous
Says when we reverse
The six of coins represents an unfair exchange or outstanding debt
You're in the middle of striking an agreement
Make sure you understand the terms completely so you don't get taken advantage of if you're indebted to others the card advise you to make
Honoring those debts of priority now. I don't know if that answered your question, but I hope it did
I hope they gave you some insight and maybe some clarity
I feel like that's sassy.
Okay, it's well up and her actually explode. Oh no.
I hope everyone's doing good.
I love you guys.
Oh, no problem, my pleasure.
How are we doing, Schmelly?
So what's going on, guys?
Just thinking what I want to do today.
Nice Wednesday.
Yeah, let's see
No, no one wants to come up. I take Adderall. You're so funny. No, I don't think Adderall. I set a lot of sleep
I'm like totally awake now
So they're smoking a little bit of pot actually
Now let's do some of this sage
What's this sage burning away?
a little rested. Well, I woke up at... Oh, I don't remember when I fell asleep, but...
I just remember I had a nice sleep.
I don't know. Looking refreshed? Yeah.
I almost don't want to leave the house right now.
Hi Justin, good to see ya.
Yeah, I saved you the room.
I saved you the room.
This place looks pretty good.
Hey, Schmelly, thank you so much
Gifted membership. Thank you so much, Melly. It's awesome
I'm got it. Do you see you got it? I was interested to know
Tommy V. Tommy V. Oh, yeah, and you're in the chat. That's awesome. Yay. Congratulations.
Yeah, see now get, you know, it was like a, you know, you're a reading,
you're free readings, they're longer. Also, I got a lot of stuff in members only,
You have access to a lot of videos now, and also you get the emoji next to your name and your name is in green.
And I'll get the emojis in chat working too.
Congratulations.
Everyone's having a great day.
That was just kind of a troll. I think he's pretty much harmless, but he is quite a troll.
Very low on weed, but I'm pretty good on tobacco.
They don't sell, they don't sell the Swisher Sweets anymore.
Can you believe it guys?
The more Swisher Sweets.
Or even no cigars at all.
They have no cigars, they just had cigarettes
and they had magazines and stuff.
I know Sam had apparently,
Has said that I am he's boycotting my showers. I don't know. I don't know here. It's okay
I don't know why but
So
McDonald's isn't bad, you know
But I don't think they have good deals in the app
Seven bucks for a big double cheeseburger 520 guys
I don't really feel like going out.
Okay, so this looks like a pretty good deal.
I can get copies and a Big Mac for it, yeah.
Donals. Yeah, I think it's almost like, you know, problem like the auto
Okay
Get like a large prize
to be on somebody else's phone to be doing the Wi-Fi in the backyard. I can't go on the
Wi-Fi in the backyard. So I have to go tablet, backyard, because as soon as I want to go to
that, like maybe the alley, maybe the no goes up. It's too far from the Wi-Fi hookup. So I have to go
I'm going to probably have to do this in Russia.
It's a bit of a jam, so I think we can go outside with the tablet.
That far.
After they took the little SIM card out, I used to be able to go around a lake with the tablet.
And then they took the SIM card out, and then you came down the street.
It's bullshit man!
You got me fucked up!
Ha ha ha
I'm gonna try this later too
This is so fucking fucked
You can't see the light
I'm gonna try it again
It's starting to get quiet!
Hello, how are you?
I'm awake
Hello, hey, you look buff today you're ripped
You oil up
No, let me fix your break for
Right now the better
Yeah, I got I got a couple of coffees. I got a french fries and they a big Mac. I got the big the big Mac was free
I'm loving it. Yeah
Nick your microphones
If you don't get part of the book, you better get it something like that.
Fuck it.
Yeah, your audio is kind of cutting out.
Well, I'll talk like real loud and like I'm Martin Luther King Jr.
Okay.
And I have some sort of dream.
Do that.
Well, you have to do your do your do your silent act because I had to mute you because your microphone is so bad
Okay, it's okay. No, we love you. We love you, Nick. We just want to look at you
They said maybe if you if you re-enter like go back and re-enter. Oh my gosh. Oh my gosh, Nick
Naked
Do we do guys we see something
Guys, what do we see are we okay you guys think I didn't see anything
What do we think guys guys you just perform on me
Nothing much, okay
Okay
Oh gosh guys
Wow, okay, okay, I'm sure was it
Why do you have Google printed out Google stock images?
I don't know.
We spoke in the bong.
Unfortunately, I mean, I do have like this vape.
The vape has probably a couple more heads of it.
It's very at the dregs.
Very dregs.
It lasted a long time though.
It's pretty good.
You're shooting yourself in the morning grass?
Yeah, so what's up for this week?
No, it's that's a June late June
Yeah, make out a new microphone
Well, at least he's nice to look at, guys, you know.
Yeah.
I'm sorry, I'm so silent
on here, you cut my microphone off, you fucking, you've done everything to try to be a fucking
Hey
answer.
Well, it's because your microphone, it sounds a little bit static-y.
A little bit static-y.
You can talk about that shit, you have a fucking allergy, you have a fucking microphone, tell
me in the chat so I can eat it big if they don't like it.
Well, yeah.
I mean, it's like, I really can't even understand, like, a word you're saying, it's just, it's
other, you're-
I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll see you later, buddy.
I'll see you later, buddy.
Oh, well, I made a map.
I mean, it didn't mean to be a map.
I'm just going to restart real quick, just in case.